

WEB DEVELOPER

Details

+54911 67834985 leanceps2@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

Skills

PHP

Python

JavaScript - jQuery

HTML5 / CSS / Bootstrap

React

SQL(MySQL - PgreSQL - Oracle)

NoSQL(MongoDB - Cassandra)

Elasticsearch

Apache / Nginx

Docker

GIT

Languages

Spanish; Castilian

English

Profile

I am passionate about software development, I like to have the **support of a team** and **learn new technologies**. I have experience applying **agile methodologies** to my work, such as SCRUM.

I like working remotely because it favors my **creativity** and my ability to **manage and plan time** correctly.

Outside the work environment, I like to travel and see new places.

Employment History

PHP Developer Full Stack, BSmart Lab, Vicente López, Buenos Alres

JULY 2021 - PRESENT

- Commercial website creation (PHP Laravel, HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, JQUERY).
- Code improvements applying design patterns and development of new utilities in the integrated platform of the Secretary of Security of Vicente López.
- Creation of new Applications/web platforms for new clients.
- Analysis and projection of new requirements/developments.
- Administration of web servers and code integrations / deployment planning.

PHP Developer Back-end, Global Hitss, Vicente López, Buenos Aires

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

- Development of new Rest APIs in Lumen & Slim microframeworks for ClaroVideo client.
- Analysis and resolution of bugs or code improvements.
- Work under agile methodologies, SCRUM & SAFe.
- Development of scripts in python to perform automated tasks.
- Development of an administrator in REACT for the use and consumption of Rest APIs.

PHP Developer Full Stack - Project Analyst, Secretary of security of Vicente López, Vicente López. Buenos Aires

JULY 2019 - JUNE 2021

- Creation of web platform (PHP Laravel, PgreSQL, JS).
- Platform integrated with the security and health forces, recording their geolocation and daily incidents within the city.

Education

Higher technical in Information Systems, UTN, Vicente López, Buenos Aires
MARCH 2019 - PRESENT

Course, Global Hitss Academy, Vicente López, Buenos Aires

SEPTEMBER 2019 - DECEMBER 2022

3 months of training on HTML, CSS, PHP, Python with MySQL and NoSQL databases.